CURRICULAM VITAE

MD. ARIFUZZAMAN

Present address:

House #07, Road # 02 Word # 3, Block # C

Kamarpara, Thana: Turag (Uttara), Post: Nishatnagor, Dhaka -1711.

Email: aponuits@gmail.com

Mobile: +8801671059585, +8801797776779.



Career Objective:

To build my career in an organization where I will be able to explore my potential by applying my academic knowledge, experience and skill for an opportunity to learn, grow and take greater responsibilities and proper utilization of educational background.

Educational Qualifications:

B.Sc. in Computer Science & engineering (CSE)

Major : WEB development, Mobile Apps Development,

Minor : Networking

Result : GPA 3.80 out of 5

Institution : University of Information Technology & Science (UITS)

Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)

Group : Science Passing Year : 2010 Result : 3.63

Institution : Dhaka Boys College

Board : Dhaka.

Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

Group : Science Passing Year : 2007 Result : 2.90

Institution : Kamarpara High School

Board : Dhaka.

Experience:

Organization name: Ha-Meem group.Designation : IT Officer (Central)

Time period : December 2013 to March 2015
Responsibility : Software Maintained ,networking,

❖ Present Organization : Mbiztech Consulting Pvt.Ltd (Devloper)

Responsibility :SEO, software development,

❖ Taught few students at from 2010 to 2011. (Photoshop, programming & graphic design)

❖ Teaching few students of class GDC & .net 2015 to present.

❖ ODesk blog site, & article writing, web-development, with MVS limited. Canada.

❖ Logo Vector Design, pencil sketch, WEB-TEC. Graphic design.

VISIT COUNTRY:

INDIA: For visiting Mangalore, Infoycis Maysur, Calcata University.

NEPAL: Katmandu, Pokhara, Citawan, Go Sala.

Thailand: Bangkok, Pattaya City

Extra-Curriculum Activities & Achievement:















- ❖ Member of IEEE student branch of UITS 2013 to present.
- ❖ Member of USA embassy center library (U.S.A Embassy-Dhaka)
- ❖ Member of UITS Computer Club IT Society from 2010 to 2013
- ❖ As a Freelancer at, **Upwork**, **Fivver**.
- ❖ Got Apple certification Mac service maintained- Apple.inc
- ❖ Got Web design Certification web summit From IUB.edu.bd,
- ❖ Got Microsoft Excel 2010 training certification from Microsoft
- ❖ Gov.bd HR training certification under HRD Foundation Bangladesh.
- **❖** Member as a Volunteer Global Giving.org USA based nonprofit company which provide volunteer & donor all over the world.
- **❖** Continued web dev. training under Ministry ICT .BD (Top −up IT)
- **❖** Member as a volunteer of Unicef, Children's Saving, Jago Foundation.

Project portfolio:

- ❖ Wev Development : http://www.banglakhobor.org/
- CMS Site: http://www.fbigroupbd.com/
- AndroidApps:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=uits.apo n.com.everconverter&hl=en

Interested job Side:

- ❖ Software Development, Mobile Apps Development
- ❖ Like to work Networking, computer Hardware, SEO
- ❖ Like to work Graphic design & web Technology
- ❖ Interested in Nano technology in computer processor.
- **Solution** Expert to PHP.net, & Android DEV,
- ❖ Interest to work Banking & Multinational Company.

Personal Information:

Date of Birth : 19nd June1991. Nationality : Bangladeshi.

Sex : Male
Religion : Islam
Marital Status : Single
Blood Group : AB+

Permanent &

Mailing Address : Md. Arifuzzaman

House # 07, Road # 02 Word # 3, Block # C

Kamarpara, Post: Nishatnagor, Turag

(Uttara), Dhaka-1711.

Contact No : +8801671059585, +8801797776779

Email Address: aponuits@gmail.com

Computer Literacy:

- Computer Fundamentals.
- Microsoft Office (All part)
- ❖ MS Excel & word
- Graphics Design (Adobe Illustrator, Video Editing Logo Design),
- ❖ Internet Browsing & operation.
- ❖ Operating system (Original/Normal Windows XP, Vista, Windows 7/8.1/10), (Linux, Ubuntu), Mac & DOS.
- ❖ PC, Notebook & Printer Assembling & Troubleshooting etc
- ❖ Web Development(HTML5.CSS.java script, PHP)

Software Reliability:

Knowing about E-clips (java), Code Block (C, C#) Math lab, Android Studio, Visual Studio, Larval, Adobe illustrator, Auto cad.

Language Skills:

Proficiency at understanding, speaking, reading, writing $\bf Bengali$ and $\bf English.$

Hobbies & Interest:

Highly interested to as a good web developer, Traveling, Pencil Sketching, Articles & Magazines, Drawing, and Music, watching Movie, Playing badminton, cricket and football.

References:

Maj. Sayed Mortaza (Retd) Executive Director (ED) Opex Group

Address: 10/Matikata, Dhaka Senanibas. **Email**: mortuza@opexgroup.com.bd

Md. Masud Rana System Engineer Bashundhara Group

Plot # 125/A, Block # A, Road No # 2 Bashundhara R/A, Baridhara, Dhaka-1229

Phone: +8801671729210 Email: <u>m-rana@bg.com.bd</u>

Declaration of Authenticity: "I CERTIFY THAT ALL THE INFORMATIONS THAT I HAVE GIVEN ARE GENUINE COMPLETE TO THE BEST OF MY KNOWLEDGE. I AUTHORIZE THE RECEIVER OF THIS CV TO VERIFY THE INFORMATION PROVIDED IN THIS RESUME".

Signature

(MD.ARIFUZZAMAN)

Date: